Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- June in Buffalo 2009, June 2009, VI.; 1 CD-ROM (38 image files in TIFF format)
  - Violinist Lina Bahn, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_23)
  - Flutist Lindsey Goodman performing Mathew Rosenblum's Under the rainbow, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_24)
  - Pianist Lisa Moore performing Martin Bresnick's For the sexes, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_25)
  - Pianist Lisa Moore performing Martin Bresnick's For the sexes with projected video, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_26)
  - Meridian Arts Ensemble performing Bruce Pennycook's Redwood Quintet, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_27)
  - Meridian Arts Ensemble performing Bruce Pennycook's Redwood Quintet, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_28)
  - Meridian Arts Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_29)
  - Meridian Arts Ensemble taking bow after June in Buffalo performance, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_30)
  - Meridian Arts Ensemble in performance at June in Buffalo, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_31)
  - Composer Philippe Manoury, with violist Christophe Desjardins and sound engineer Christophe Lebreton at sound console, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_32)
  - Composer Philippe Manoury and violist Christophe Desjardins, with Christophe Lebreton and unidentified sound engineer at sound console, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_33)
  - Composer Bernard Rands in rehearsal with Jean Kopperud, Jon Hepfer, Jon Nelson, and Brad Lubman, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_34)
  - Composer Bernard Rands talking to mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley during rehearsal of Rands Now again, with conductor Brad Lubman and the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_35)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki and small chimes, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_36)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki with small chimes, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_37)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins in motion, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_38)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Portraits
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.